[
  {
    "question": "What is the second largest lake by area?",
    "answers": ["Superior", "Tanganyika", "Erie", "Lake of the Woods"],
    "correct": ["Superior"],
    "id": "01"
  },
  {
    "question": "What vegetables were used during halloween as Jack-O-Lanterns before pumpkins?",
    "answers": ["Turnips", "Watermelons", "Potatoes", "Aubergines"],
    "correct": ["Turnips"],
    "id": "02"
  },
  {
    "question": "‘Correlation’ can be used to describe a relationship between a quantitative and qualitative variable.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": ["False"],
    "id": "03"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first known written language?",
    "answers": ["Sumerian", "Latin", "Arabic", "Egyptian hieroglyphics"],
    "correct": ["Sumerian"],
    "id": "04"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the indigenous nation LA resides on?",
    "answers": ["Tongva", "Kalmath", "Ho-Chunk", "Cherokee"],
    "correct": ["Tongva"],
    "id": "05"
  },
  {
    "question": "Was the word orange first given to the color or the fruit?",
    "answers": ["Fruit", "Colour"],
    "correct": ["Fruit"],
    "id": "06"
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal are hyenas most closely related to?",
    "answers": ["Cats", "Wolves", "Elephants", "Rats"],
    "correct": ["Cats"],
    "id": "07"
  },
  {
    "question": "Denmark primarily uses the Euro as its form of currency.",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": ["False"],
    "id": "08"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the highest selling album of all time?",
    "answers": ["Thriller", "Led Zeppelin II", "The Dark Side of the Moon", "Rumors"],
    "correct": ["Thriller"],
    "id": "09"
  },
  {
    "question": "About how many bones does the average human adult have?",
    "answers": ["206", "503", "2", "128"],
    "correct": ["206"],
    "id": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "About how many bones does the average human infant have?",
    "answers": ["270", "206", "25", "350"],
    "correct": ["270"],
    "id": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is this?",
    "answers": ["Dave Miller", "Aubergine Man", "William Afton", "Jack F. Kennedy"],
    "correct": ["Dave Miller", "Aubergine Man", "William Afton"],
    "id": "12"
  }
]